<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
<name>MeatCore 血肉重铸 Bio-Anomaly Flesh Reforged</name>
<author>幽月琉璃Luna</author>
<packageId>lunaglaze.Anomaly.BiotechnologyReforgedFlesh</packageId>
<modVersion>0.4.7</modVersion>
<modIconPath>Items/Resource/BRF_RecastFleshCube</modIconPath>
<supportedVersions>
	<li>1.5</li>
	<li>1.6</li>
</supportedVersions>
<url>https://github.com/LunaGlaze/RimWorld-BiotechnologyReforgedFlesh-Anomaly</url>
<description>
An mod based on the Anomaly DLC that may contain elements of biopunk, meatcore, body modification, SCP, and other group weirdness creations.

“当我带来死亡时，那些受害者的生命并没有逝去，它们只不过被重新组合成了全新的事物……感谢我的仁慈吧！它们的生命在我手中被重铸，从此获得了高贵的新生——那些卑劣的生命将成为我们的一部分，从此以我的名义继续在这个世界存活下去。”

原生血肉如此苦弱，生命的奥秘带来重铸，以此铸造飞升之基。

Inspiration for the mod includes Scorn,VFE Insectoids 2, Minecraft mod Biomancy, Terraria's Crimson, Warframe's Infested, Cultist Simulator, a handful of designs from SCP and Backrooms, and more! ...... Some of this relevant content is still WIP, so stay tuned.

一个基于异象DLC的有关血肉科技、生物朋克、肉核、人体改造的模组。

[h1]Substance|内容[/h1][list]
[*] 从将在道德上不建议食用的肉类转化为似乎没有道德问题的肉和使用生物的肉培育蠕动的活体肉块开始的血肉科技。
Flesh tech starting with converting meat that is not ethically recommended for consumption into meat that seems to have no ethical issues and using the creature's meat to cultivate wriggling, living hunks of meat.
[*] 将来自实体的素材改造成守卫自己基地的力量。包括炮塔和能拿起你的武器攻击敌人的固定傀儡等。
Transform the material from the entity into a force that guards your base. These include turrets and stationary golem that can pick up your weapons and attack enemies.
[*] 归属于自然分类的血肉仿生体，从普通到超凡，包括神圣的白虫与脑蛞蝓。
The flesh bionics attributed to the natural classification include a set of medical ones with a set of fleshbeast ones, even brain slugs.
Flesh abionics of various natural categories, ranging from mundane to archotech, including the akuloth and brain slug.
[*] 建造生物机械来运营和装点你的殖民地，收获受害者超过原版可获取内容的全部器官来构造它们。
Build biomachines to run and decorate your colony, harvesting victims over the full range of organs more than vanilla to construct them.
[*] 新的实体和挑战，也包括了少数对原版实体的加强。
The new entities and challenges also include a few enhancements to the vanilla entities.
[*] 一套基于原版拓展框架的生物营养管道系统，以及你能想到的与其功能联动的生物朋克设备，比如经典的湿件伺服器……你不需要原版拓展框架来体验这个mod，但安装它能让你获得管道系统和更好的体验。
A bio-nutrient plumbing system based on the Vanilla Expanded Framework, and as many bio-punk devices as you can think of linked to its functionality, such as the classic wetware server ...... You don't need VEF to experience this mod, but installing it will give you access to the plumbing system and a better experience!
[*] 来自欲肉教（也许）的古怪的外来者。
[*] Creep Joiner from Sarkicism (maybe).
[*] 一些可以构建血肉生态的组件，例如血肉菌毯和血肉植物。
[*] Some components that can build a flesh and blood ecosystem, such as flesh and blood bacterial blankets and flesh plants.
[*] 使用血肉科技制造的医疗用品。
[*] Medical supplies manufactured using flesh technology.
[*] 血肉构造的强大枪械与刀剑。
[*] Powerful guns and swords made of flesh.
[*] And so on
[/list]
[h1]Projected|计划[/h1][list]
[*] 与其他DLC的联动和支持。
Linkage and support with other DLC.
[*] 更多强大的超凡血肉仿生体。
More powerful archotech flesh bionts.
[*] 更多的实体和威胁；如果顺利的话，可能添加四个终极的血肉领主。
More entities and threats; possibly including four new Flesh Lords.
[*] 如果我获得了美术上的帮助或者得到的支持足以让我在维持生活之余定制相关材质，我会尽我所能添加更多Metacore/血肉风格的装饰性内容。
l do my best to add more Metacore/flesh style decorative content if I get help with the art or get enough support to customise the relevant textures while maintaining a living.
[*] 终极的血肉生物装备，包括护甲、武器等等……
The ultimate flesh creature gear, including armour, weapons and more ......
[*] 一些我的支持者希望我加入的适合这个mod主题的内容，如果我可以做到的话。
What some of my backers would like me to include that fits the theme of this mod, if I can do it.
[*] ......
[/list]
[h1]Caveat|警告[/h1][list]
[*] 该模组仍然处于开发中，现行版本为测试版本，可能会存在较为频繁的改动与修复。为保证您的存档不因此损坏，建议积极进行备份。
The module is still under development and the current version is a beta version, which may be subject to more frequent changes and fixes. To ensure that your archive is not corrupted, it is recommended that you actively back up your files.
[*] 由于缺乏美术资源、能力与资金，本mod的纹理素来自包括本人个人绘制、使用不同的AI辅助制作、修改原版或其他来源材质等来源，质量与风格统一程度存在一定问题，敬请谅解。
Due to the lack of art resources, ability and funds, the textures of this mod come from sources including my personal drawing, using different AI-assisted production, modification of vanilla or other sources of textures and other sources, please understand that there are some problems with the degree of unity of quality and style.
[*] 本模组发布前只在作者个人的游戏环境下测试，无法保证完全不存在bug和兼容性问题，如果遇到相关问题，建议及时进行反馈。但一些我不会游玩的mod恕我没有能力提供补丁与修复，例如Combat Extended、Humanoid Alien Races、Vanilla Psycast Expanded、Medieval Overhaul等。如果出现问题，我可能需要你们的帮助以解决。
This mod is only tested in the author's personal gaming environment before release, and there is no guarantee that it is completely free of bugs and compatibility issues, so if you encounter any related problems, it is recommended that you provide feedback in a timely manner. However, some mods that I won't be playing forgive me for not being able to provide patches and fixes, such as Combat Extended, Humanoid Alien Races, Vanilla Psycast Expanded, Medieval Overhaul, and so on. If a problem arises, I may need your help to fix it.
[/list]
[h1]Language|支持语言[/h1][list]
[*] English(fully support)
[*] 简体中文（完全支持）
[*] 繁體中文（完全支持）
[/list]
[h1]Credit|特别鸣谢[/h1][list]
[*] 感谢 切丁鱼片 提供的 静电囊泡、血肉荧光囊泡与管道系统出入液口 原始美术资源。
[*] Thanks to 切丁鱼片 for providing the original art resources of : Electrostatic Vesicle, Glow Flesh Bulb, Nutritional Tap, Nutritional Drain.
[*] 感谢 应天装备制造所 提供的 绯红蕈 原始美术资源。
[*] Thanks to 应天装备制造所 for providing the original art resources of : Crimson Agarilux.
[*] 感谢 应天装备制造所 为血肉枪械系列装备 绘制参考图像。
[*] Thanks to 应天装备制造所 for help to drawing the reference images for the flesh gun series equipment.
[*] 感谢 羊羊羊乃乃乃 提供的 重生灵骸 原始美术资源。
[*] Thanks to 羊羊羊乃乃乃 for providing the original art resources of : Rebirth Psycorpse.
[/list]
[h1]Links|连结[/h1][list]
[*] [url=https://github.com/LunaGlaze/RimWorld-BiotechnologyReforgedFlesh-Anomaly] Github [/url]
[*] [url=https://patreon.com/shiqiluna] Patreon [/url](I probably don't use it that often)
[*] [url=https://afdian.com/a/shiqiluna] 爱发电 [/url](Available to Chinese users)
[/list]

</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>ludeon.rimworld.anomaly</packageId>
			<displayName>RimWorld - Anomaly</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
<loadBefore>
</loadBefore>
<loadAfter>
	<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
	<li>ludeon.rimworld.Anomaly</li>
	<li>ludeon.rimworld.Biotech</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Odyssey</li>
	<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
	<li>Ogliss.Ykara.HarvestEverything</li>
    <li>anomaly.corpration</li>
    <li>rim.job.world</li>
</loadAfter>
  <incompatibleWith>
    <li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
    <li>Dajian.ChiTeaditional.Expanded</li>
  </incompatibleWith>
</ModMetaData>